这是您点的今日鱼餐
Here's your fish of the day.
小姐  不好意思
Excuse me, miss?
我的烘肉卷里有根头发
There's a hair in my meatloaf.
这事情绝对是个案
This never happens.
奥列格
Oleg!
T-2里有H-34
We got a H-34 at T-2!
毛发吗  不可能啊
A hair? That's impossible.
我先把裤子穿上
Let me put some pants on.
我深表遗憾
I am so sorry
您居然点了烘肉卷吃
that you ordered the meatloaf.
他不是应该戴个发网吗
Shouldn't he be in a hairnet?
他最应该的是进监狱
He should be in a prison.
好消息
Good news.
这根不是我的
It's not mine.
我的生发剂真的很有效啊
That Propecia's really paying off.
这也很明显不是我的  我是金毛丫头
Obviously, it's not mine. I'm blonde.
你也不是全身都"金毛"啊
You're not blonde everywhere.
我就爱听人聊"地毯跟窗帘"
I love carpet-and-drapes talk.
我想要回我的钱
I want my money back.
我也想
Me too.
这根也不是我的
Well, it ain't mine.
我还有这么长的头发那会
Last time my hair was this long,
还是我80年代在歌舞节目当舞者的时候呢
I was a back-up dancer on Solid Gold.
阿憨
Han!
我们有个龟毛屁事多的顾客
We got a customer with a hair up his butt
他的后肉卷里也有根毛
and one in his meatloaf.
一边去
Step aside.
待本山人一看究竟
Let an expert through.
是电视剧《法律与秩序  特殊受矮者》
Look, it's "Law and Order: SAD"
棕色毛发  介于咖啡色与深褐色之间
It's brown, somewhere between coffee and burnt sienna,
用洗发沐浴混合露潦草清洗过
cleaned hastily with a combination shampoo-body wash.
这根头发的主人是个单身狗白人
Mm, this hair belongs to a single white man
是没人爱  而非想单身  而且注定单身到死...
alone, and not by choice, but so set in his ways--
够了
Okay!
是我的头发
It's mine!
下次想骗吃骗喝
Next time you want a free meal,
记得点今日鱼餐
order the fish of the day.
对吧  女士
Am I right, ma'am?
我能点个东西吗
Hey, can I order something?
你得先出示证件
I'm gonna need to see some ID.
我又想浪迹天涯了
I'm getting the itch to hit the road again
需要个新身份
and I'll need a new identity.
我要一杯莫斯科驴子
I'll have a Moscow Mule.
来一杯综合水果饮料酒吧
Uh, how about a Jolly Rancher shot?
这是我们的招牌饮品之一
They're one of our signature drinks,
杯中还会以我的指枪点缀呢
served with a side of my finger-guns.
来一杯莫斯科驴子如何
How about a Moscow Mule
毕竟我刚才点的就是这个
since that's what I just ordered?
你确定吗
Oh, are you sure?
烈酒杯是用真的水果饮料杯来装的呢
The shot glasses are made of actual Jolly Ranchers.
小孩特爱呢
Kids love 'em.
一杯莫斯科驴子马上来
One Moscow Mule coming up.
好咧
All righty.
你不知道怎么调  对吧
You don't know how to make one, do you?
完全不会
No clue.
那我自己来调如何
How 'bout I just make it myself?
既然你都动手了  给我来杯杰克和可乐
Hmm, while you're at it, I'll have a Jack and Coke.
一直都想知道这酒是用什么调出来的
Always wanted to know what was in that.
麦克斯  那个男的在你身后干嘛
Max, what's that guy doing behind you?
你明知道男人在我身后干嘛时我从不回头看
You know I never look when they're back there.
你不能让别人自己给自己服务
Look, you can't let people serve themselves.
不是什么哪里都是自助餐店好吗
Again, not everything is a Hometown Buffet.
如果这里是  我已经在吃
Uh, if it were, I'd be eating a biscuit
饼干通心粉加布丁了
with macaroni and pudding on top.
顾客都不点我们的招牌酒饮
People aren't ordering our signature drinks.
他们要喝真的酒
They want real ones,
但我只会调我们菜单上有的那些
and I only know how to make the stuff on the menu.
还有摇头丸加棒棒糖  我叫它"加棒"
And Molly lollipops, which I call "Mollipops"
那还是我来调吧
Then let me do it.
我万圣节后昏睡三天就是因为你的"特调酒"吗
And is that why I slept for three days after Halloween?
我能要灰狗吗
Can I get a greyhound?
灰狗...
Greyhound...
我已经不在灰狗巴士开大巴了
I don't drive for them anymore.
政策啥的
Politics!
喂  有人点单了
Uh, you heard the man.
我们付钱给你可不是让你在这白站着
We're not paying you to just stand around.
你们压根就没付我钱
You're not paying me at all.
就你这态度还想挣钱
Not with that attitude.
相信我  我们要是够钱请酒保  早就请了
Believe me, if we could afford a bartender, we'd hire one.
看来这合作关系是合不来了
This obviously isn't working out for either of us.
给你的服务有啥问题吗  小费呢
Was there a problem with your service?
麦克斯  我们得谈谈昨晚发生的事
Max, we need to talk about what happened last night.
靠  你明明说你有在吃事前避孕药
Oh, crap, you said you were on the pill.
我们甜品酒吧需要有个人
We need someone at the dessert bar
懂得怎么调真正的酒饮
who knows how to make real drinks.
绝不是嫌弃你的"烟屁股汤力"销量不好
Not that your "Cigarette butt and toni" wasn't a hit.
是你说我们请不起酒保
You said we couldn't afford a bartender...
或是买机械牛
or a mechanical bull,
要是当时买了  现在早赚回本了
which would have paid for itself by now.
我有个主意
Here's my idea.
我们可以去上调酒课  这样...
We are going to bartending school so we can--
别踹我  我们就能成为
and don't kick me-- be the best--
别捏我  也别打鼻子
no pinching, not my nose--
一家我们想成为的好店
business we can be!
我弹
G'doink.
你没说不能弹
You didn't say anything about G'doinks.
你觉得如何
What do you think?
因为我们已经报名付费  而且不能退钱了
'Cause we're already signed up and it's non-refundable.
我从你的存钱小猪烟斗里拿了你的学费
I took your share out of your piggy bong.
你居然从招财跟进宝里偷钱
You stole from Cheech and Change?
你不喜欢我这主意  说就是了
Okay, you can say you hate the idea,
你不需要哇哇哭吧
but you don't have to cry about it.
这孩子裤裆里的屎[一派胡言]多到
Man, this baby's more full of crap
比酷玩乐队专辑里还多
than a Coldplay album.
我现在替你换尿布  但等你长大了
Fine, I'll change your diaper, but when you grow up,
记得还我这份情  也替我换
you're going to have to return the favor.
尿布包反了
The diaper goes the other way!
厄尔  是那个娃娃说话了
Earl, did that doll just talk
还是脑海中的声音又让我开始杀戮了
or are the voices telling me to kill again?
不是  这娃娃吼了我一整天了
No, no, it's been yelling at me all day.
除了这个  还有我助听器
Between this and the police chatter
接收到的警察无线电
I pick up on my hearing aid,
我脑子里就跟开派对似的
it's like a damn party in my head.
收到
Roger that.
这个娃娃还能再更吓人一点吗
Can this doll get any creepier?
卡洛琳  你也好不到哪去
Takes one to know one, Caroline.
你问了  她答了
Asked and answered.
一位淑女就不能抽烟撒尿时
Can't a lady have a smoke and a tinkle
不用操心着自己的孩子吗
without having to worry about her baby?
你刚才从厕所里在偷看我们吗
You were watching us from the toilet?
你不能像别人一样捂鼻子从隔间上方偷看吗
Can't you just hold your nose and hover like everyone else?
这是我的监控娃娃  你看
It's my surveillance doll. Look.
它连接到我手机里的一个软件了
It's hooked up to an app in my phone.
看  她...
Look, she's got
眼珠里有摄像头
cameras in her eyeballs;
嘴巴有个麦克风
she's got a microphone in her mouth;
屁眼还有个激光指示器
and look, a laser pointer in her butt.
这是美国女孩娃娃之爱国者法案版吗
Is that the American Girl Doll PATRIOT Act edition?
她是不是超可爱
Isn't she cute?
就像是我的双胞胎姐妹
Look, she's like my twin,
差别只在比我更活生生
only more alive.
谢谢你替我留心照顾芭芭拉
Thank you for keeping your eye on Barbara.
非常谢谢你
Well, thanks so much.
我很乐意付你钱
I'd pay you,
但我知道你骄傲的自尊不容许自己收下钱
but I know you're too proud to take the money.
苏菲  其实我的药费单堆积如山...
Uh, actually, the medical bills are piling up, Sophie.
-再见啦  -我其实还挺需要...
-Well, see you later! -And I could really use...
如果你需要免费保姆  找他
If you need a free babysitter, that guy.
是我的问题
Is it just me
还是店里又热又雾蒙蒙
or is it hot and blurry in here?
先生  失礼了
Pardon me, sir.
天啊  阿憨
Oh, my God, Han.
你浑身起了斑  还有幻觉
You're covered in spots and you're delirious.
你长水痘[鸡痘]啦
You have chicken pox.
你也还有小鸡腿  所以你也算齐活儿啦
You also have chicken legs, so I guess you're even.
阿憨  你得回家隔离
Han, you have to go home.
你这病有传染性
You're contagious.
而且不是我笑声这种好的传染性
And not like my laugh.
欢迎来到餐厅堡威廉斯
Welcome to the Dinersburg Williams.
那胡话谁说的
Who said that?
是你说的  你必须得回家
You did! You have to go home.
我的确不介意回家躺床上
Well, I suppose I could get into bed
在线看点《明迪烦事多》
and Hulu a little Mindy Project.
哎妈  她可真"人生计划"啊
And, boy, is she a project.
阿憨看起来不太稳定
Han looked pretty unsteady.
你觉得该找人确保他安全回家吗
Do you think someone should make sure he gets home okay?
别杞人忧天  他没事的
Don't worry so much. He'll be fine.
你看  没事
See? Fine.
我知道这只是调酒课
I know this is just bartending class,
但麻烦吐出口香糖
but gum, please?
告诉你  这其实是嚼用烟草
That was chewing tobacco, FYI.
麦克斯  我们得认真上课
We need to take this seriously, Max.
那是小折刀吗
Is that a pocket knife?
是啊
Uh, yeah.
我要是不在桌子上刻名字缩写
How are they gonna know I was here
他们怎么知道我在这上课
if I can't carve my initials in the desk?
或许我们俩不应该坐在同一个工作台
Maybe we should sit at separate workstations.
我很明显会是班级尖子生
I'm obviously gonna be the top student here
我不想跟你那
and I don't want to be associated with your
"又叛逆又没医保"的姿态扯上关系
"rebel without health insurance" attitude.
随便你  拜拜
Fine, smell you later.
你好
Hi.
我毕业后就没上过课
I haven't been in a class
我是从沃顿商学院毕业的
since I graduated from Wharton.
-是常春藤盟校...  -我哈佛大学毕业的
-It's an Ivy League-- -I went to Harvard.
沃顿是我当年的保底学校
Wharton was my safety school.
麦克斯  你的小折刀还在吗
Max, do you still have that pocket knife?
好了  我看大家应该都到了
Okay, I think everyone is here.
大家好  我叫吉尔·布朗斯基
Hi, my name is Gil Bronski
我完全不着急下班回家
and I am in no rush to go home.
我跟我母亲以及她的三只猫同住
I live with my mother and her three cats,
其中两只最近在拉稀
two of whom have diarrhea.
我还以为是搞笑开场呢
I thought it was an icebreaker.
不  是地毯开花了
No, it's a carpet-ruiner.
谢谢捧场  朱莉
Oh, thanks, Julie.
朱莉大杀四方啊
Julie's killing it.
我想你们大家都在好奇
Now, you're probably all wondering,
"眼前这位前童星
"How did this former child actor
因为30年的毒瘾而短暂坐冷板凳
Briefly sidelined by a 30-year drug addiction
是怎么沦落到来教人调酒呢"
find himself teaching bartending school?"
因为撞大运了吗
Just got lucky?
就是撞大运了
Just got lucky!
你们谁能回答这题
Now, who can answer this?
他都还没问呢  马屁精们
He hasn't asked it yet, ass-kissers.
丘吉尔喝着长岛冰茶宣布开战
Churchill declared war while sipping a Long Island Iced Tea.
大宪章鸡尾酒  法国大革命鸡尾酒
The Magna Carta, French Revolution,
我的三次离婚
my three divorces,
它们的共同点在哪里
what's the common denominator?
酒啊  废话
Booze, duh.
Booze, duh!
她没举手
She didn't raise her hand.
哎哟  貌似来了一些装认真逼啊
Boy, we have got some eager beavers here, don't we?
上班午餐时间  鸡头也对我们说了这句话
Ha, that's what my pimp told us at our working brunch.
其实呢
Now...
我个人只有一个规矩
I have only one rule.
不许...
No--
打断我
Interruptions.
这不可能  都六年没人给我打过电话了
This is crazy; no one has called me in six years.
我还以为更久了呢
I would have guessed longer.
谢谢捧场  朱莉
Thanks, Julie.
大家来调酒吧
Let's make some drinks!
我的天啊  我爱死上学了
Oh, my God. I love school so much.
我为什么应该知道
How am I expected to know the difference
伏特加日出跟伏特加日落的差别在哪啊
between a vodka sunrise and a vodka sunset?
差了12小时与少了一条裤子
12 hours and a missing pair of pants.
别吵  我在学习
Now, shh. I'm studying.
这是我这辈子第一次做功课
That was the first homework I've ever done.
我从来没见过你对一件事这么上心
I've never seen you take anything this seriously.
之前得狂犬病你都没这样
And you had rabies once.
别胡闹了  这是为了学校呢
Stop joking around. This is for school.
你从哪里弄来的眼镜  《黄金女郎》吗
Where did you get those glasses, The Golden Girls?
这是我这辈子第一次想好好"的"学习呢
For the first time in my life, I want to learn goodly.
麦克斯  我们是互换了身体吗
Max, have we switched bodies?
如果真是这样  好好享受性病吧
If so, enjoy chlamydia.
我想考试考高分
I want to do well on this test.
我想得到...
I want to get a, uh...
高分的那个字母是啥来着
what's the good letter?
是得A
It's an A.
我想这大概是我这辈子第一次得不到了
And I think this is gonna be the first time I don't get one.
我完全看不进去这些教材
I am just not connecting to the material.
就像是科幻喜剧  好好选一方向不行吗
Like sci-fi comedy, I mean, pick a lane.
把那本书给我
Well, give me that book
因为老娘要搞定这次调酒考试
'cause I'm gonna nail this bartending exam
就像搞定超市里认识的陌生男人一样
like it's some guy I met at the grocery store.
我大部分的考试结果上面都写着"来办公室见我"
Most of my tests just had "See me" written at the top.
我的总是写着
Mine always had,
"你又成功了  卡洛琳·钱宁"
"You've done it again, Caroline Channing"
我必须再次成功  让我做杯喝的试试
And I have to do it again. Let me try making a drink.
好的  酒保
Okay. Bartender?
给我做杯血腥玛丽
Make me a Bloody Mary.
要喝的哦  不是我那个
The drink, not my friend Mary Nichol
四年级就来大姨妈的朋友玛丽
who got her period in fourth grade.
我必须会做这个
I have to get this.
我知道血腥部分是用番茄汁
I know the bloody part is tomato juice,
但玛丽是什么鬼啊
but what the hell is the Mary?
我应该知道的呀  毕竟我跟很多玛丽约会过
I should know. I've dated so many.
我给你个提示吧
I'll give you a hint.
跟"屎莫加"最后一字相同
Rhymes with "Schmodka"
哥得加
Grodka!
这都不是个字  我真是脑抽了
That's not even a thing. What is wrong with me?
应该是伏特加
Vodka.
那是蛤蜊汁
Um, that was clam juice.
我当然知道
Sure was.
上菜  新鲜出炉的...
Pick up, hot...
娃娃
doll.
苏菲娃娃
The Sophie doll?
上面全是头发
Well, it's covered in hair
所以在这里可以算是食物啦
so it'll pass as food around here.
替我扔了它就行
Just get rid of it.
苏菲时不时用它来批评我
Sophie's constantly using it to criticize me,
所以我断开了她连接的软件
so I disconnected her app.
我是说  她到底要为了这事嚷我多少遍啊
I mean, how many times can she yell at me
不就是上完厕所后要洗手吗
to wash my hands after going to the bathroom?
每次都该嚷吧
Every time?
这个娃娃快逼疯我了
That doll is driving me crazy.
再说了  我觉得自己...
Plus, I think I'm...
要开始爱上它了
starting to have feelings for it.
好吧  给我吧
Fine. I'll take her.
我好久没有鬼娃娃了
I haven't had a possessed doll
鬼娃恰吉在2009年就搬走了
since Chucky moved out in '09.
他能做"血腥"玛丽
Now, he could make a Bloody Mary.
还能做"血腥"丹妮丝  还有"血腥"胡里奥
And a bloody Denise and a bloody Julio.
一说起死回生的恐怖娃娃  就真来一个
Speaking of creepy dolls come to life.
阿憨  如果会传染  你就必须待家里
Han, if you have open sores, you have to go home.
虽然你的员工也都不是有传染病就待家里
Not that it's stopped anyone else who works here.
我有家回不得
I can't go home.
我为了止痒洗了个燕麦浴
I took an oatmeal bath to get rid of the itching,
结果公寓被淹了
and it flooded my apartment.
我试着吃了它
I tried eating it down,
结果昏倒  还差点窒息身亡
but I passed out and nearly suffocated.
找个好点的地铁长凳  蜷在上面
Well, find a nice subway bench to curl up on.
或者赛百味的三明治也行
Or even a Subway sandwich.
你知道如果被一个没上过床的家伙传染得病
You know how embarrassing it would be to catch a disease
这事有多丢脸吗
from a guy I haven't slept with?
干嘛  我牙齿上有东西吗
What? Do I have something in my teeth?
当然有  但问题不在牙齿
Yes, of course. But not that.
麦克斯  你好像也得了水痘
Max, I think you have chicken pox.
我可以让你少丢一点脸
Well, I could make this less embarrassing for you.
我们可以上床啊
We could have sex.
真不敢相信那只小病猴居然
I can't believe that little Outbreak monkey
把水痘传染给我
gave me the pox!
如果他落入我的手套里  那我一定
If I get my mittens on him, I'm gonna tear him
把他撕成碎片
from tiny limb to tiny limb.
那我最好还是待在浴室别出来吗
Best I stay in the bathroom then?
不
No.
出来吧  第一感染源病友
Come on out, patient-zero-friends.
我需要你输入你的网飞视频网密码
I need you to enter your Netflix password.
密码是"打憨机69"
It's "Han job 69."
你给我设的啊
You're the one who set it.
谢谢你让我暂住在你家
And thanks for letting me crash here.
我不确定你能否合法将我变成你一辈子的男佣
I'm not sure you can legally make me your butler for life,
但我的确签了卖身契
but I did sign the contract.
我还觉得有点头晕眼花
I'm still feeling a little woozy.
你好呀  苏菲
Hello, Sophie.
少给我转移话题
Don't change the subject.
老娘第一次这么想去学校
For the first time, I really wanted to go to school.
我知道我可以把你的头塞进我马桶
I know I could fit your head in my toilet,
但我很好奇我能不能把你整个身子塞进去
but I wonder if I can get your whole body in there.
你的"婊气"真是气得我浑身"痒"
Wow, you really put the "bitch" in "itch."
能帮我挠挠吗
Could you?
就是这样
Ah, that's the stuff.
现在换你帮我挠
Now get my back.
爽不爽  够不够力
You like that? Is it hard enough?
我会不会弄疼你了
Am I hurting you?
你少自作多情以为自己"猛"了
Don't flatter yourself.
我没爽够前不许停
Don't stop till I get enough.
让麦克斯把上衣脱掉不是更方便吗
Won't that be easier if Max takes her shirt off?
奥列格
Oleg!
你是在监视我们吗
Are you spying on us?
妈妈
Momma.
我完蛋了我
I am so screwed.
离调酒考试还有两小时
The bartending test is in two hours,
而我却记不住白色佳人酒里面有啥
and I can't remember what goes in a White Lady.
一瓶夏敦埃酒下肚
A bottle of chardonnay
一个逗她发笑的肥佬就可以进入"里面"
and then a fat guy that makes her laugh.
那是卡洛琳吗
Is that Caroline?
她的声音听上去像没穿内衣
She sounds like she's not wearing underwear.
奥列格怎么会在一个娃娃"里面"
How did Oleg get inside the doll?
真希望我是第一次说这话
Wish it was the first time I said that.
我下了那款软件
I got the app,
现在我也有周六夜"现场"了
and now I have a Saturday night.
奥列格  你有看见我的苏菲娃娃吗
Oleg, have you seen my Sophie doll?
没有看见呢
Uh...I haven't seen her.
先挂啦
Gotta go.
等等  这玩意什么手机都能用吗
Wait, this thing works with any phone?
天啊  麦克斯  我们可以利用这个娃娃
Oh, my God, Max, we can use the doll
这样你就可以在考试时把酒的配方告诉我
so you can read me the ingredients for drinks on the test.
你是说作弊吗  在学校作弊吗
You mean cheat? At school?
哇  或许我们真的互换了身体
Wow, maybe we did switch bodies.
-胡说  还是平的  -谢天谢地
- Rats. - Oh, thank God.
我能不能让你们俩其中一个
Is there any way I could get either of you
帮我挠挠肚皮呢
to scratch my tum-tum?
给
Here.
指甲触感好真实哦
The nails are real.
上衣不错啊  书呆妹
Nice shirt, nerd.
上衣不错嘛
Ooh, nice shirt.
谢谢  布先生
Thanks, Mr. B.
要夸夸我的上衣吗
Any love for my shirt?
感觉拍马屁用力过猛
Mm, feels desperate.
麦克斯呢
Hey, where's Max?
我们一帮人打算课后一起去吃饭
A bunch of us are going to Chili's after class.
麦克斯生病了  但我有空
Max is sick, but I'm totally free.
只预定了10个人的位子
Mm, reservation's only for ten.
但麦克斯不在  我可以坐她的位子啊
But Max isn't here, so I can take her spot.
想得美
You'd think.
那是什么
What's that?
那是我的精神支柱娃娃
Oh, this is my emotional support doll.
帮她梳头有助于让我平静
I brush her hair and it calms me down.
我可不是疯子
I'm not insane.
这话我都说了30年了
Hey, I've been saying that for 30 years!
好了  孩子们
All right, kiddies,
10分钟做10杯鸡尾酒
I need ten drinks in ten minutes.
有次喝得断片的我曾说过
Or, as a blacked-out me once said,
"让开对派始吧"
"Let's get this starty parted."
开始
Begin.
麦克斯  你在吗
Max, are you there?
你看见桌上分好的材料了吗
Can you see the set-up?
我看见你和朱莉俩人
I see you and Julie both
都在马屁精服饰店买衣服
shop at Tommy Bah-Brown Nose.
你的可可里要加肉桂条吗
Care for a cinnamon stick in your cocoa?
当我没问  一只千足虫把肉桂条拿走了
Never mind, a millipede carried it off.
学校怎么样  有人问起我吗
How's school? Did anybody ask about me?
帮我向基思问好
Tell Keith whassup.
还有向戴夫问好  不过别当着基思的面
And tell Dave whassup, but not in front of Keith.
麦克斯  别分心
Max, focus.
我要做的第一杯鸡尾酒是尼格龙尼
The first drink I have to make is a Negroni.
我马上就告诉你怎么做
And I'll tell you how to make it
只要你先帮我给杰夫捎个话
as soon as you relay a message to Jeff
原话是这样的
that goes a lot like this:
你好啊啊啊
whassup.
麦克斯说"你好啊啊啊  你好啊啊啊"
Max says, "Whassup, whassup."
好了  你快说
Okay, I'm listening.
琴酒
Gin.
不  那不是琴酒
No, that's not gin.
你难道没念过幼儿园吗
Did you even go to kindergarten?
是它旁边那瓶
It's the one right next to it.
知道了
Got it.
我真的在作弊耶
Wow, I am really cheating.
我真是个坏女孩
I am such a bad girl.
做好了  阿憨特调热可可
Here we go, hot cocoa Han-style.
上面加了一层泡沫棉花糖
Complete with a frothy marshmallow layer.
棉花糖
Ooh, marshmallows.
还有棉花糖  知道了
And marshmallows, got it.
不不不  不是跟你说
No, no, no, not you.
我刚才在跟瑞士小姐说话呢
I was talking to Swiss Miss over here.
啊...
Aah...
嚏
choo.
天啊  你比我跟踪
Man, you are acting crazier than me
汤姆·汉克斯那会还疯
when I was stalking Tom Hanks.
没事  没事
It's okay, it's okay.
你洒得整本书都是
You spilled all over the book.
我一个字都看不清了  怎么会没事
I can't read a thing. How is this okay?
因为...
Because...
有事的是你的可可
that was your cocoa.
你现在喜欢你的女佣瑞士小姐了吗
How do you like your girl Swiss Miss now?
你最好赶紧拿东西把书擦干
You better grab something to dry this book off.
书擦干  那是一种伏特加吗
Bookoff? Is that a vodka?
我好恐慌  我要挂科了
I'm panicking. I'm gonna fail.
调酒考试居然作弊
Aw, cheating on a bartending test?
我要把对《战火迷情》剧组说的那句话送给你
I am gonna tell you the same thing I told The Situation:
你还是滚回老家吧
you take it on back to Jersey.
说得好  布先生
Good one, Mr. B.
谢谢  朱莉
Oh, thanks, Julie.
非常抱歉  布朗斯基老师
I am so sorry, Mr. Bronski.
只要让我通过  我什么都愿意做
Please don't fail me. I'll do anything.
但不上床
But nothing sexual.
毕竟这只是学调酒的学校  不值得我卖肉
I mean, after all, it's just bartending school.
这个娃娃归我了
I'm gonna take this doll with me.
她来填补今晚餐厅多出的空位
She's gonna be our tenth at Chili's.
布先生  你好呀啊啊
Hey, Mr. B, whassup!
你好呀  麦克斯
Hi, Max.
我至今无法忘记那个画面
I just can't get it out of my head.
太可怕了
It was terrible.
他当着我的面把娃娃撕成两半
He ripped apart the doll right in front of me.
接下来这部分我都不好意思告诉你
And then this part I couldn't even tell you,
我...
I f...
-挂科了  -放屁了
- Failed? - Farted!
你也知道我一难受  肚子也跟着难受
You know how my stomach gets when I'm upset.
如果能让你觉得好过些
Well, if it makes you feel any better,
我醒来时发现我跟阿憨相拥而眠
I woke up with me and Han spooning.
你是拥人还是被拥人
Which spoon were you?
后面被小鸡鸡顶了三个小时的人
The one with the stiffie in her back for three hours.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
我们只是过来喝一杯综合水果饮料酒
We just stopped in for a Jolly Rancher shot
然后就去看现场做爱秀了
on our way to a live sex show.
苏菲  宝宝呢
Sophie, where's the baby?
她跟保姆在一起
Oh, she's with the babysitter.
某个变态混蛋偷了我的苏菲娃娃
Some perverted SOB stole my Sophie doll.
我意识到
I realized that
其实不用一天24小时 一周8天都看着芭芭拉
it's okay not to watch baby Barbara for 24-8.
在波兰  我们一周会多一天
You know, in Poland, we get the extra day.
拿来疏浚湖泊
For dredging the lakes.
要不你去找张桌子坐下吧  苏菲
Why don't you go get us a table, Sophie?
好的
Okay.
还有机会把娃娃拿回来吗
Any chance of getting that doll back?
我真是低估了我之前对它的爱有多强烈
I really underestimated how strong my feelings for it were.
我知道
I know.
就是我不小心撞见你帮她梳毛发的啊
I was the one who walked in on you brushing her hair.
也是我让你别把这事说出去的啊
And I was the one who asked you not to repeat that.
我要一杯莫吉托
I'll have a mojito.
抱歉  我们不做点单上没有的酒
Sorry, we don't do off-menu drinks.
我来吧
I'm on it.
一杯莫吉托  马上好
One mojito coming up.
你这是做什么  我们明明挂科了
What are you doing? We failed the class.
我第一次说这话时不放屁
Ooh, first time I didn't fart saying that.
是你挂了
You failed.
在学习和帮你作弊的时候
Between studying and helping you cheat,
我学会了做那本书上所有的鸡尾酒
I learned how to make every drink in that book.
天啊  麦克斯  你真的有学到东西
Oh, my God, Max, you learned something.
我挂了是为了让你能成功
I failed so you could succeed.
所以在某种程度上  我也成功了
So in a way, I succeeded too.
你又成功了  卡洛琳·钱宁
You've done it again, Caroline Channing.
太爽了
Oh, yeah!
原来现场做爱秀是在这里
Oh. The live sex show is here.